You want to ban drag show readings to children.
To minors, yes.
Why?
What are you protecting?
Why can we prohibit children from voting,
those under 18 from voting?
Why are you banning...
But also that.
Is that free speech?
Are you infringing on that performer's free speech?
They can continue to exercise their free speech,
just not in front of a child.
Why?
Because the government does have a responsibility to protect...
I'm sorry?
The government does have a responsibility in certain...
What's the leading cause of death
amongst children in this country?
And I'm going to give you a hint.
It's not drag show readings to children.
Correct, yes.
So what is it?
I'm presuming you're going to say it's firearms.
No, I'm not going to say it like it's an opinion.
That's what it is.
It's firearms.
More than cancer, more than car accidents.
And what you're telling me is,
you don't mind infringing free speech
to protect children from this amorphous thing that you think of.
But when it comes to children that have died,
you don't give a flying fuck.
To stop that because that shall not be infringed.
That is hypocrisy at its highest order.